INSERT INTO `achievements` (`achievement_id`, `achievement_no`, `about`, `pic`, `content`, `date_entered`) VALUES ('1', 'A001', 'भारत विकास परिसद - समूह गान प्रतियोगिता (2017) ', 'achievements/a001.jpg', 'स्थानीय और नियोजन नीति में संसोधन को लेकर सत्ता पक्ष के विधायक गोल बंद हो गए हैं।', CURRENT_TIMESTAMP), ('2', 'A002', 'भारत विकास परिसद - समूह गान प्रतियोगिता (2018)', 'achievements/a001.jpg', 'त्रिपुरा में भाजपा के वाम मोर्चो के 25 साल के शासन का अंत करने के करीब पहुंचने के बीच प्रदेश पार्टी अध्यक्ष बिप्लव देब ने आज कहा कि वह मुख्यमंत्री पद की जिम्मेदारी लेने को तैयार हैं, लेकिन इस बारे में फैसला भाजपा संसदीय बोर्ड को लेना है. जिम इंस्ट्रक्टर से नेता बने देब ने भारी समर्थन के लिए त्रिपुरा के लोगों का आभार जताया और प्रधानमंत्री नरेंद्र मोदी और भाजपा अध्यक्ष अमित शाह को पार्टी के शानदार प्रदर्शन का श्रेय दिया.', CURRENT_TIMESTAMP), ('3', 'A003', 'भारत विकास परिषद् - भारत को जानो प्रतियोगिता (2017)', 'achievements/a003.jpg', 'We participate in the co-curricular activities such as swimming, scouting, N.C.C., school band, skating, singing, dancing, etc. Students having unfair behavior and undisciplined activities are punished by the class teacher as per the school norms. Our principal takes classes of every student daily in the meeting hall for 10 minutes to deal with our character formation, etiquette, moral education, acquiring good values and respecting others. Our school time is very interesting and enjoyable as we do lots of creative and practical works daily. Our oral assessment of storytelling, singing, poem recitation, conversation in Hindi and English is taken by the class teacher on daily basis. So, my school is the best school of the world.', CURRENT_TIMESTAMP), ('4', 'A004', 'भारत विकास परिषद् - भारत को जानो प्रतियोगिता (2017)', 'achievements/a004.jpg', 'स्थानीय और नियोजन नीति में संसोधन को लेकर सत्ता पक्ष के विधायक गोल बंद हो गए हैं।', CURRENT_TIMESTAMP);